magportal.com 2002-06-07

# Privacy Policy (MagPortal.com)

**Location: ******| Help / Privacy Policy  
---|---  
Hot Hot Neuron LLC respects your privacy and we have drafted this document to try to address any concerns that you may have about the information we collect and how it is used on MagPortal.com. Hot Neuron LLC may revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this policy periodically. 

_Last revised: $Date: 2001/12/01 00:13:32 $_

**What personally identifiable information is collected?**  
We do not currently require users to provide any personally identifying information (name, email address, street address, etc.) to use the MagPortal.com service. In the future, we may require such information in exchange for providing additional services, such as but not limited to: delivery of physical products, entrance into a sweepstakes, or the privilege of posting on message boards. If you send correspondence to us, we may store a copy (which means that we will have your email address and name). 

**What are cookies and how are they used on MagPortal.com?**  
A "cookie" is a small piece of data that is sent from a web site such as MagPortal.com to your computer where it is stored on your hard drive. When you access that web site in the future, your browser sends that cookie back to the web site, which allows the site to recognize you as someone it has seen before. 

MagPortal.com makes use of cookies so that it can provide you with personalized services such as My Articles. We may also use cookies to help us monitor your use of MagPortal.com for the purpose of generating aggregated statistics and targeted advertising and content on our site in order to increase its usefulness to you. 

Please be aware that our advertisers and service providers may use cookies of their own which we do not control (more information is given below). 

If you do not wish to have MagPortal.com use cookies to identify you, you can turn off cookies in your browser. Disabling cookies will make some personalization features of MagPortal.com unusable. 

**How are IP addresses used?**  
An IP address is a set of numbers assigned to your computer when you connect to the internet. 

The MagPortal.com site records the IP addresses of people using the site. This information may be used for monitoring the use of the site or reporting aggregated statistics. This information may also be used when we feel it is necessary to protect our site, enforce our Terms of Use, or enforce the law. 

**Advertisers and Third Parties**  
Please be aware that advertisers on MagPortal.com and third party sites which MagPortal.com links to are not subject to the MagPortal.com privacy policy. Our advertisers may use cookies for various reasons. They may, for example, use cookies to avoid showing you the same advertisement many times, to measure which ads you respond to, or to track your behavior when you leave the MagPortal.com site. 

Statement provided by DoubleClick on their ad serving policy: 

> We [MagPortal.com] use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm). 

Hot Neuron LLC does not provide personally identifying information (e.g. your name, email address, etc.) that we collect from you (for example from feedback which you email to us or your subscription to our mailing lists) to third parties unless it is with your explicit consent (generally for the purpose of providing an additional contracted or co-branded service) or if we believe in good faith that it is necessary for the enforcement of the law or our Terms of Use agreement. We do not rent or sell your personal information. 

We may provide aggregated statistics about the users of MagPortal.com to third parties. 

**Security Information**  
You should keep your password secret and be extremely cautious when using shared computers. Be sure to remove the MagPortal.com cookie from any public computer you use and exit the browser to ensure that nobody else can access your personal information. 

Please be aware that whenever data is transmitted or stored there is always some risk of theft or misuse. 

Help   Home   Site Map   Privacy Policy   Terms of Use   Contact Us   Advertise Copyright © 2002 Hot Neuron LLC. All Rights Reserved.  
MagPortal.com and Hot Neuron are service marks owned by Hot Neuron LLC.
